MUHAMMAD RISQI FIRDAUS

Software Engineer

Bandung, Indonesia | HP: 082245200501 | Email: 13520043@std.stei.itb.ac.id Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mrfirdauss/ | Github: https://github.com/mrfirdauss-20

SUMMARY

An undergraduate informatic student with experience as web and chat bot developer. Love building and developing technological things. Specialized in web development using various stacks (PHP, Node js, Python). Able to quickly learn and adapt to new technologies and teams.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Skillup - Bandung, Indonesia

Vice Manager of Technology (September 2021 - Now)

• Developing and coordinating team on web development.

Hikeryco – Bandung, Indonesia

Chief Technology Officer (July 2021 - Now)

- Developing websites using php and mysql for web services.
- Deploying the web via ID Cloudhost VM platform and maintaining DNS for www.hikery.co.

Schoolpad.id - Bandung, Indonesia

Quality Assurance (September 2020 - Desember 2020)

- Checking and testing the quality of try out questions that will be served for the user.
- Checking any bugs on the website, try out system, and user experience.
- Analyze posts for social media promos and marketing.

EDUCATION

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI BANDUNG (2020 - Now)

B.Eng, Informatic Engineering - GPA 3.10

PROJECTS

Wecome - KM ITB x Ditmawa ITB

Fullstack Developer (September 2021 - Now)

Welcome is website that provides competition information for ITB student. Built the first version website using php mysl. I responsible for building the backend system and deploying.

Konsul.in

Backend Developer (January 2021)

Konsulin is consultation web that built for muslimhackfest 2021. I Responsibled for leading the development team. Develop Whatsapp chatbot and website services using node js. Maintaining the JQuery for the websites. Deploying the web via Heroku.

Web Image Compression

Backend Developer (November 2021)

The web is built using python flask. This web provides image compression using SVD decomposition. I responsible for building the backend using python flask, and set the upload and compression mechanism.

ADDITIONAL

Technical skills: Python (Matplotlib, Pandas, Seaborn, Sklearn), MySQL, C++, NodeJs, PHP, Problem Solving, Web Development, Excel (Linkedin Certificate)

Language: English, Arabic

Certifications and training: Latihan Mujtahid Dakwah 208 Masjid Salman ITB Awards: Semifinalist of Muslim HackFest 2021, Semifinalist HackGov UGM 2021